morning and here are your top five
stocks to watch out for this Monday
morning well it's a whole H ster of a
mix of results as well as some stocks
which are in the news so let's begin
then with oil India uh with Union Bank
rather first stop which came out with
its quartery numbers well on the face of
it the pat number looked encouraging at
332 CR rupees for q1 this is versus 224
CR rupees on a year- on-ear basis you
had the nii growth as well which came in
healthy at
6,43 CR rupes versus
2518 crores the provisions this time
around remain slightly elevated at
around
3,555 crores versus about 3,51 crores on
a QQ basis the gross uh npas came in at
14.95% versus 14.15 per with net NPS at
4.97% versus 4 5.49% which means they
were fairly stable on a QQ basis moving
on to another set of numbers and then
watch out for oil India in today's
trading session as the revenue from
operations came in significantly lower
at
1749 CR rupees for The Quon by versus
about
3,380 crores the profits dwindled to
just about 26 crores versus
847 CR rupees there was an exceptional
item in q1 of about 93 crores that was
incurred and that was on account of the
control in the blowout in uh bjan oil
field you operational performance as
well was hit very significantly to 181
crores versus 1353 CR rupees with Martin
coming in at a mega 10.4% versus 40% y y
clsa maintains a cell with a Target at
60 saying the bottom line has
disappointed there was a beaten a bitar
but one offs led to a net loss in q1
they've raised the EPS forecast but
retain a sell rating meantime watch out
for India Bull's housing as well which
came out with its quarterly numbers you
had the profits which dropped about 65%
uh the company said that the loan book
is growing though from here on because
they seeing a phase of reduction in the
loan book in AUM so 272 CR Pat versus
790 crores revenue from operations
dropped nearly 35% to
2574 CR rupees and the company has said
that the covid pandemic has
significantly impacted the numbers
including erosion of the asset values of
the collateral that has been held by
their individual segments ICI Lombards
in Focus clsa has a buy rating with a
Target price at1 1560 they're saying
that the bti AXA merger is a near term
EPS di dilutive they see significant
Headroom for cost optimization and the
rational for merger is strong bti AXA is
in the motor segment and the scale and
energy is going to help ICICI Lombard to
optimize their expense Futures in uh
expense ratio in the future PVR aay ble
has gone ahead and said that they're
hopeful of of a Resurgence due to the
pandemic once the government does allow
cinema halls to reopen he says that PBR
will diversify and not rely on any
single Revenue stream but he's
optimistic that expansion remains on
track he said that it will not change
the movie goinging habits of people and
they will continue to come to theaters
he has said that uh people are not going
to be hardwired to stay at home and
footfalls will be back to pre-o levels
soon they already are right now in some
of the Delhi malls the revenues are down
to zero but they are tackling the
disease which he says will take top
priorities so they are going to go ahead
they are talking about that Drive-In
Cinema that the company is looking at
they are ready to open their theaters
they will be following Sops and all of
the uh safety procedures